projectpayday.com 2016-10-31

# Project Payday - Realistic Extra Income for the Average Joe

**Project Payday Privacy Policy**

We take your privacy very seriously, and we've created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy.

This page outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

**_What information does Project Payday collect from visitors?_**

Project Payday collects information from our visitors and users of our website and uses the information internally for marketing and administration purposes, in the fulfillment of our service commitment to you, or as required under the law.

As a user of this website, Project Payday may collect your personally identifiable information when you visit our site and create a Project Payday account.

The personally identifiable information that we collect is limited to just your name and email address. Members will also supply a phone number and mailing address.

Project Payday is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.

**_Why is information collected?_**

Information may be collected in an effort to enhance your user experience, provide you with information regarding Project Payday services and special offers, and/or to provide you with the products and/or services you request.

We, or our authorized third-party affiliates, may also collect general information about purchases as they correspond to our advertisements or products. This aggregate information may include demographic and usage information, but will not include personally identifiable information.

This information is used in an aggregated manner (i.e. How many customers purchased product "X") to determine advertising effectiveness and is sometimes shared with our advertising partners for the same limited purpose.

In addition, information is collected for the following purposes:

  * Upon creating an account you must provide your name and email.
  * Certain actions may cause you to be eligible for a cash rebate. We issue rebates via PayPal or a check in the mail. If you request your rebate via check, you will need to provide us with your mailing address.
  * When ordering products or services your information will be collected for purposes of payment, product delivery and/or customer service.
  * By registering at our web site and creating a Project Payday account, you'll be added to our internal mailing list. As a registered user, we may contact you about customer service related issues, functionality changes to the web site, account updates, new services, and special offers.
  * Members may called about additional products and services related to their membership.

**_How does Project Payday protect my information?_**

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information. Users' personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by certain key employees.

Should it be necessary to transmit your personally identifiable information to a reputable third party vendor to fulfill our service commitment to you, Project Payday will require all recipients of such information to maintain the information as confidential information, use the information for the limited and intended purpose and agree not to disclose such information.

**_Will Project Payday disclose the information it collects to others?_**

Project Payday does not rent or sell any of the information collected by this website with other people or any other companies, except to provide the products or services you've purchased or requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Project Payday's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about Affiliates who promote Project Payday and earn over $600 in commissions in a calendar year;
  * To confirm your membership and/or offer additional products and services by phone via a third party;
  * We may share your user information with carefully selected and well-respected service providers or other companies that provide marketing services on our behalf or to other providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

In addition, you agree that registering at our web site constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR section 310 et seq. (the "ATSR"). With respect to the ATSR, and notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, Project Payday and affiliated entities retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the terms of the ATSR.

**_Does Project Payday use "cookies" or pixel "tags"?_**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow website operators to better customize a site to your individual preferences.

The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and most major websites use them. We may use cookies to help provide you with a better experience on our site; however, we do not store personally identifying information in cookies.

Like many Web sites, Project Payday may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement.

We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies, and limit the collection of information for the same purpose. We do not store personally identifying information in pixel tags.

**_Can I access or modify the Personal Identifying Information collected?_**

You can view and/or modify the information provided to us at any time by logging in to your account, and clicking the "Account Info" link. You may also submit your request to modify your account information via any of the methods below.

**_What if I want to Opt-Out of email communications from Project Payday?_**

Project Payday provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future promotional communications from us. You may do so in the following ways. Please note however that even if you opt-out, you may still receive important announcements or updates regarding your Project Payday account.

1\. Email: [support@projectpayday.com](mailto:support@projectpayday.com)  
2\. Website: http://www.projectpayday.com/unsub.cgi  
3\. Postal Mail: 1675 Larimer St, Suite 640, Denver CO 80202

**_Project Payday Research_**

By registering at Project Payday, you automatically become a member of our survey panel research program, ProjectPaydayResearch.com. As such, you will receive the opportunity to participate in paid research studies. You can manage your ProjectPaydayResearch.com account by logging in [here](http://www.projectpaydayresearch.com/).

**_What happens if there is a transfer of Project Payday's business?_**

As we continue to develop our business, we may acquire or divest various business assets, or be acquired ourselves. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred assets.

In the event of such a transaction you will be notified prior to your personally identifiable information being subject to a new Privacy Policy, and given the opportunity to opt-out should you desire to do so.

**_Can children or minors use Project Payday?_**

Project Payday does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from or about anyone under the age of 18. If we discover we have received such information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe Project Payday has any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us. If you are under 18, you may not use Project Payday.

**_Links to Other Sites_**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Project Payday is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**_Your consent_**

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide per this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. If this policy is changed, we will post these changes on this page so you are always aware of the information we collect and how we use it.

**_Contacting Project Payday_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy statement, the privacy-related practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via one of the methods above for immediate assistance.

This Privacy Policy was last updated January 20th, 2014.
